Guide to the New Almaden Mine (Calif.) Collection, 1845-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES IV: LEGAL DOCUMENTS, 1846-1945
  - GENERAL, 1853-1945
    - Agreements, 1892-1927, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Application, 1911 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Assignments, 1910, 1916 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Authorization, 1912 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Berryesa title index, n.d. (Volume 46)
    - Bills, 1863-1912 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Bonds, 1873-1910 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Claims, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Consent forms, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Contracts, 1863-1917 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Conveyance, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Court appearances, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Debuture, 1870 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Declaration of trust, 1861 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Discharge of charges, 1882 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Estray animal, notice of taking possession, 1916 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Fire insurance, 1925-1926 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - List of papers, 1869 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda, 1853-1924 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Newsclippings, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Notices, 1870, 1911-1912 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Opinions, 1866 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Permit, 1914 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Plan for Mr. Robert, 1920(Re: bankruptcy sale of land) (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Power of attorney, 1864, 1883 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Records (Volume 47)
    - Records, received and delivered, 1889 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Records, transcribed, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Receipts, 1857-1910 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Releases, 1863-1885 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Remittance, 1915 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Reports, 1901-1910 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Request, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Right of way, 1872, 1884 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Safe, list of contents, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Settlement, 1911 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Statements, 1864, 1920 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Writ of attachment, 1908, 1911 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - LITIGATION, 1850-1927
    - Adams v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1867-1869 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Anderson v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1915 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Bailey v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1872 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Barclay v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1872 (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Barrow v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1868 (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Berryessa v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1856-1874 (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Black v. Eldridge, 1864 (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Butterworth v. Hermann, 1864 (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Cazares v. New Almaden Company and the Ocean Accident and Guarantee Corporation, 1927 (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - Costello v. Brown (The Quicksilver Mining Company), 1905 (Box 80, Folder 40)
    - Forbes v. Berryessa, 1855 (Box 80, Folder 41)
    - Freaner and Addison v. Butterworth (The Quicksilver Mining Company), 1867, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 42)
    - Furlong v. New Almaden Company, Incorporated, 1927 (Box 80, Folder 43)
    - Gray v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1885 (Box 80, Folder 44)
    - Gray v., last half (Volume 48)
    - Gray v., abstract of bill and demurrer (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Gray v. Taylor, 1850 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Hamilton v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1884 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Jeffers v. Santa Clara Mining Association of Baltimore, 1876 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Johnson v. Middleton, 1870 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Knowles v. Taylor, 1869 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Knox and Osborne v. Huttner and Scott, interference, 1878 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Knox and Osborne v. Huttner and Scott, interference, 1878 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Knox, and Osborne v. Huttner and Scott, interference, opposition (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Knox, and Osborne v. Huttner and Scott, furnaces, claims, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Knox and Osborne v. Quicksilver Mining Company, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Knox, and Osborne v. Quicksilver Mining Company, vol. II, exhibits (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Knox and Osborne v. Quicksilver Mining Company, vol. II, pleadings to exhibits (Volume 49)
    - Knox and Osborne v. Quicksilver Mining Company, notes, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Middleton v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1881 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Middleton v. Gray and Walker, 1850, 1853 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Moran v. Depau, 1916 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Notes, ca. 1867-1868 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - O'Brien v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1882 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1867 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - People (of California) v. Billings, 1864 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - People (Harry A. Nichols) v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1912 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Probate numbers, Knowles Taylor, Francesca Gomez, John B.Gray, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Quicksilver Mining Co. vs. C.P. Anderson, 1917 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Quicksilver Mining Company, Voluntary dissolution, court transcript (Volume 50)
    - Quicksilver Mining Company v. C.P. Anderson, appeals, 1917 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - The Quicksilver Mining Company v. Hicks, 1867-1868 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - The Quicksilver Mining Company v. Santa Clara Mining Association, ca. 1865 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - The Quicksilver Mining Company v. Williams, 1876 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Sambrano v. New Almaden Company, Incorporated and The Ocean Accident and Guarantee Corporation, 1921 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Santa Clara Mining Association of Baltimore vs. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1879 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Frank J. Sullivan v. Charles N. Felton, contested election case, 1887 (Volume 51)
    - Tatham v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1916 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Taylor v. The Quicksilver Mining Company, 1860 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Thornes v. Hepburn, 1854 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - United States v. Guadalupe Mining Company, 1858 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - United States v. Andres Castillero, 1859-1861 (Volume 52)
    - Valencia v. Berryessa, 1853-1863 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Walker v. Gray, 1885 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Walker v. Taylor, 1857, 1869, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - PATENTS, 1864-1887
    - Agreements, 1885, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Assignment of ownership, 1877-1882 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Indentures, 1881, 1884 (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - License, 1880 (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Memoranda, 1867-1882 (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Patents, 1864-1879 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Permission to use, 1878-1884 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Power of Attorney, 1886 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Release, 1884 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Reports, 1876-1887 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Trademarks, 1873, 1882 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - REAL ESTATE, 1846-1915
    - Abstract of title, 1876 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Abstract of title, Rancho de los Capitancillos derived through John Middleton, 1-220, 1876 (Volume 53)
    - Abstract of title, Rancho de los Capitancillos derived through John Middleton, 221-442, 1876 (Volume 54)
    - Abstract of title, Rancho de los Capitancillos derived through John Middleton, 661-880, 1876 (Volume 55)
    - Abstract of title, Rancho de los Capitancillos derived through John Middleton, Santa Clara County, Vol. II, 187? (Volume 56)
    - Abstract of title, James Eldridge to a portion of the Rancho de los Capitancillos..., n.d. (Volume 57)
    - Aromitas y Acqua Caliente, 1862 (Box 7)
    - Boundary descriptions, 1846-1867 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Boundaries, property measurements, 1863-1864, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Deeds, 1851-1876 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Descriptions of property, 1846-1867 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Indentures, 1859-1890 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Indentures, 1892-1900 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Indentures, 1900-1915 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Indentures, copies of, notarized, ca. 1855-1865 (Volume 58)
    - Indentures, and contract/record book (Volume 59)
    - Land grant, 1869, 1874 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Land sales, 1910-1911 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Leases, 1865-1871 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Leases, 1 Jan. 1872 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Leases, 1 July 1872-1877 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Leases, 1903-1924 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - List of deeds, 1866 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Mortgage, 1863 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Rent, ground rent lists, 1876-1878 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Rents, 1904 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Salispuedes, 1861 (Box 7)
    - Salispuedes, title papers, ca. 1865 (Box 7)
    - Sheriff's certificate of sale, 1863 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Transfers, 1850-1915 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Tenant's agreements, 1865-1877 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- SERIES V: FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1851-1942
  - EUREKA COMPANY RECORDS, 1894-1910
    - Sales, accounts, 1894 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Sales, accounts, 1895 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Sales, accounts, 1896 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Sales, accounts, 1897 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Sales, accounts, 1898 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Sales, accounts, 1899 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Sales, accounts, 1900 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Sales, accounts, 1901 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Sales, accounts, 1902 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Sales, accounts, 1903 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Sales, accounts, 1904-1905 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Sales, accounts, 1906 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Sales, accounts, 1907-1908 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Sales, accounts, 1909-1910 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Sales, distribution of surplus, July 1901-Sept. 1902, Sept. 1905-Sept. 1906 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Shipments, quicksilver, Jan.-Feb. 1903, June 1907 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - NEW ALMADEN COMPANY INCORPORATED RECORDS, 1915-1925
    - COMBINED INCOME/EXPENDITURES
      - Accounts current, 1922-1923 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Balances, opening/closing, 1920-1922
      - Balance sheets, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Balance sheets, 1918 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Balance sheets, 1919 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Balance sheets, 1920 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - Balance sheets, 1921 (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Debit/credit accounts: New York office, 1917-1919 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - Income and expense accounts, 1918-1921 (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - Operations, monthly resume, June 1915 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - Operations, summary of, 1918-1921 (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Operations, summary of, 16 Dec. 1920 (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - Revenues and expenses, 4 Feb. 1915-30 Apr. 1918 (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - Revenues and expenses, report by Klink, Bean and Company, 31 Dec. 1919 (Box 7)
      - Trial balances, Apr.-Dec. 1915 (Box 87, Folder 18)
      - Trial balances, Apr. 1915-Dec. 1920 (Box 87, Folder 19)
      - Trial balances, cattle account, 1915-1916 (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - Trial balances, Apr.-Dec. 1916 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Trial balances, Apr.-Dec. 1917 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - INCOME
      - Cash demand notes, 1916-1921, 1924-1925 (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - Leaser's production accounts, 1916-1917 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Quicksilver price quotations, Oct. 1914-Apr. 1919 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Sales, report, 19 Jan. 1921 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Shipment notifications, 1915-1916 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - Shipment notifications, 1915-1916 (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - Shipment notifications, 1920-1921 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - EXPENDITURE
      - Cash receipts, Mar. 1915-July 1919 (Box 88, Folder 10)
      - Cash statements, July-Dec. 1916 (Box 88, Folder 11)
      - Cost, construction, Senator furnace, 1917-1918 (Box 88, Folder 12)
      - Cost, construction, Scott furnaces, 1920 (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - Cost per ton statement, Jan-June 1917 (Box 88, Folder 14)
      - Cost sheets, 1917 (Box 88, Folder 15)
      - Cost sheets, 1918 (Box 88, Folder 16)
      - Cost sheets, 1919 (Box 88, Folder 17)
      - Cost sheets, 1920 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Cost sheets, 1921 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Cost sheets, 1924 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Expenses, general, 1917-1919 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Leasers' ore purchases, 1916-1917 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - Operating costs, 1918-1919 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Payroll, labor, segregation of, 1916, 1919 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - Production costs, 1917 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - INVENTORY
      - Equipment, depreciation and depletion on, 1917-1921 (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - Equipment, insurance listing, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - Equipment, list of. Sept. 1917 (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - Equipment, 1917-1920 (Box 89, Folder 12)
      - Equipment purchases, May 1915-Dec. 1919 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - NEW ALMADEN COMPANY INC./NEW ALMADEN STORES INC. RECORDS, 1915-1924
    - COMBINED INCOME/EXPENDITURES
      - Accounting suggestions, 5 Jan. 1915 (Box 89, Folder 14)
      - Accounts, closing, 1917-1920 (Box 89, Folder 15)
      - Accounts, statements, 1909, 1915, 1917 (Box 89, Folder 16)
      - Accounts, statements, 1921-1924 (Box 89, Folder 17)
      - Assets and liabilities, statement of, 1917, 1919-1920 (Box 89, Folder 18)
      - Balance sheets, consolidated, 1919-1920 (Box 89, Folder 19)
      - Income and expense accounts, 1916-1921 (Box 89, Folder 20)
      - Operations report by Klink, Bean and company, 1915, 1918, 1918 (Box 89, Folder 21)
      - Operations report by Klink, Bean and company, May 1920 (Box 7)
    - INCOME
      - Accounts receivable, 1921 (Box 89, Folder 22)
      - Income account statement, 31 Mar. 1921 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - EXPENDITURES
      - Cash receipts and disbursements, reports on, Jan. 1916-Jan. 1921 (Box 89, Folder 24)
      - Cash receipts and disbursements, reports on, Dec. 1916-Dec. 1921 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - NEW ALMADEN CORPORATION RECORDS, 1940-1941
    - INCOME
      - Licensee's sales and production tables, 1940-1941 (Box 89, Folder 26)
      - Licensee's sales receipts, 1940-1941 (Box 89, Folder 27)
      - Licensee's sales receipts, to Coast Chemical Division, 1940 (Box 89, Folder 28)
      - Licensee's sales receipts, to Pacific Vegetable Oil Corporation, 1940-1941 (Box 89, Folder 29)
      - Licensee's sales receipts, to Pacific Vegetable Oil Corporation, 1940-1941 (Box 89, Folder 30)
      - Licensee's sales receipts, to New Almaden Corporation, 1941 (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - NEW ALMADEN QUICKSILVER MINES CORPORATION RECORDS, 1916-1924
    - COMBINED INCOME/EXPENDITURE
      - Audit, by Bertron Griscom and Company, 8 July 1924 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Balance sheets, opening, 30 June 1916 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Balance sheets, opening, May 1924 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Trial balance, 1917-1918 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - NEW ALMADEN STORES INCORPORATED RECORDS, 1915-1922
    - COMBINED INCOME/EXPENDITURES
      - Balances, opening/closing, 1918-1921 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Balance sheets, 1918 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Balance sheets, 1919 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Balance sheets, 1920 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Balance sheets, 1921-1922 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Income and expense accounts, 1918-1921 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Trial balances, 1915-1917 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - Trial balances, cattle account, 31 Dec. 1915 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - EXPENDITURES
      - Cash statements, July-Oct. 1916 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - QUICKSILVER INVESTMENT COMPANY RECORDS, 1915-1924
    - COMBINED INCOME/EXPENDITURES
      - Account by Bertron Griscom and Company, Jan. 1924 (Box 90, Folder 14)
      - Account by Bertron Griscom and Company, 26 June 1924 (Box 90, Folder 15)
      - Trial balance, 30 Apr. 1915-31 Oct. 1916 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - QUICKSILVER MINING COMPANY RECORDS, 1851-1921
    - COMBINED INCOME/EXPENDITURE
      - Accounts, current, Apr. -July 1864 (Box 90, Folder 17)
      - Accounts, current, 1864 (Box 90, Folder 18)
      - Accounts, current, Jan. -June 1865 (Box 90, Folder 19)
      - Accounts, current, July-Dec. 1865 (Box 90, Folder 20)
      - Accounts, current, Jan.-June 1866 (Box 90, Folder 21)
      - Accounts, current, July-Dec. 1866 (Box 90, Folder 22)
      - Accounts, current, 1867 (Box 90, Folder 23)
      - Accounts, current, 1892 (Box 90, Folder 24)
      - Accounts, current, 1894-1895 (Box 90, Folder 25)
      - Accounts, current, 1898-1900 (Box 90, Folder 26)
      - Accounts, current, 1902-1905 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Accounts, current, 1907-1909 (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Account statements, 1851-1855 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Account statements, 1871 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Account statements, 1872 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Accounts and records, 30 Apr. 1913 (Box 7)
      - Balance sheets, 1891 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Balance sheets, 1909-1909 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Trial balances, 1865-1867 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Trial balances, 1915-1916 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - INCOME
      - Accounts, interest, 1866-1868 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Account of sales, C.J, Brenham, 1864-167 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Account of sales, Bright Brothers, 1864-1866 (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - Account of sales, Butterworth, 1864-1865 (Box 91, Folder 13)
      - Account of sales, Butterworth, Jan.-Nov. 1865 (Box 91, Folder 14)
      - Account of sales, Butterworth, Nov. 1865-July 1866 (Box 91, Folder 15)
      - Account of sales, Butterworth, Aug.-Dec. 1866 (Box 91, Folder 16)
      - Account of sales, Butterworth, Jan.-June 1867 (Box 91, Folder 17)
      - Account of sales, Butterworth, July-Dec. 1867 (Box 91, Folder 18)
      - Account of sales, Butterworth, 1892-1895 (Box 91, Folder 19)
      - Account of sales, Butterworth, 1897 (Box 91, Folder 20)
      - Account of sales, Butterworth, 1900-1905 (Box 91, Folder 21)
      - Account of sales, Butterworth, 1907-1909 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Sales report, 1914-1915 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Sales report, 31 Jan. 1921 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Shipments, invoices of, Aug.-Sept. 1882 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Shipments, invoices of, Oct.-Dec. 1882 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Shipments, invoices of, 1883 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Shipments, invoices of, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Shipments, notices, 1882, 1883 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Shipments, receipts, 1864-1867 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - EXPENDITURES
      - Cash receipts, June-Nov. 1913 (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Cash receipts, Apr.-Dec. 1914 (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Cash receipts, 1915 (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Cash statements, 1889-1890 (Box 92, Folder 13)
      - Cost of work sheets, 1908-1909 (Box 92, Folder 14)
      - Creditor list, 1917 (Box 92, Folder 15)
      - Expense account, general, Oct. 1913 (Box 92, Folder 16)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1864, 1868-1870 (Box 92, Folder 17)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1868-1870 (Box 92, Folder 18)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1872, 1889-1890 (Box 92, Folder 19)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1874-1876 (Box 92, Folder 20)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1880 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1881 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1882 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1883 (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1883 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1884 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, Mine, Jan. 1889-Aug. 1890 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, Hacienda, Jan. 1889-Aug. 1890 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1903-1905 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Mine and Hacienda accounts, 1907-1909 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - INVENTORY
      - Boarding house, 1885 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Boarding house, 1 May 1899 (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Boarding house, 1 June 1900 (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Boarding house, 1906 (Box 93, Folder 14)
      - Casa Grande, 1908 (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - Flasks, 1 Sept. 1863-24 Oct. 1863 (Box 93, Folder 16)
      - General account, inventory, 1874-1876 (Volume 60)
      - General, for insurance, Jan. 1873 (Box 93, Folder 17)
      - General, for insurance, 4 June 1915 (Box 93, Folder 18)
      - Mine tools, 1902 (Box 93, Folder 19)
      - Office, 1915 (Box 93, Folder 20)
      - Senator mine store room, 4 May 1920 (Box 93, Folder 21)
      - Sexton house, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 22)
- SERIES VI: EMPLOYEE PAPERS, 1848-1945
  - HEALTH AND WORKMEN'S COMPENSATION, 1889-1945
    - California Metal Producer's Association, The Necessity of Safety Work (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Coroner's verdict, 1909 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Industrial Accident Commission, findings and awards, 1919, 1926 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Industrial Accident Commission, Workmen's Compensation, Insurance, and Safety Laws, 1917 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Insurance, accident report, Colonial Mutual Compensation Insurance Company, Limited, 1944-1945 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, Industrial Accident Commission, 1917-1919 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Insurance, physician's report, 1940 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Insurance, supplemental, 1917-1918 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Insurance, United States Fidelity and Guaranty Company, 1917-1925 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Insurance, application for adjustment of claim, 1918-1926 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Insurance, claim, 1917 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Insurance, compensation, sequence for, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Insurance, continuation certificate, 1919 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Insurance, court order, 1926 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Insurance, notices, 1917-1926 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Insurance, payment/compensation receipt, 1945 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Insurance, policy endorsements, Nov. 1927 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Physicians industrial examinations, 1942 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Physician's monthly reports, 1889-1892 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Salivation, how to avoid, 1918 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - PAYROLL RECORDS
    - Advance book, Hacienda and Mine payroll, supply lists, 1882-1883 (Volume 61)
    - Payroll, Guadalupe mine, 1881-1882 (Box 94, Folder 21)
      Did not reprint - did correct p 6.
    - Payroll, Hacienda, 1904-1907 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - Payroll, Hacienda, 1908 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Payroll, Hacienda, 1909 (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - Payroll, mine, 1904, 1907 (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - Payroll, mine, 1909 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - Payroll, New Almaden Company, general, 1915-1920 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Payroll, New Almaden Stores, 1917-1919 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Payroll, New Almaden Stores, 1920-1922 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Payroll, Senator mine, 1916 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Nov. 1918 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Dec. 1918 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Jan.-Feb. 1919 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Mar. 1919 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Apr. 1919 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, May 1919 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, June 1919 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, July-Aug. 1919 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Sept.-Oct. 1919 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Nov. 1919 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Jan.-Feb. 1920 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Mar.-Apr. 1920 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, May-June 1920 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Feb.-Apr. 1921 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, May-June 1921 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, July-Dec. 1921 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Jan.-Feb. 1922 (Box 97, Folder 2)